- id: ckw-l31-5289
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カロリー
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5293
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コーチ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5301
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - サイクル
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5309
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - タンク
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5333
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パートナー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5338
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ファースト
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5338
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レート
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5345
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - キャベツ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5345
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - フロー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5355
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レモン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5361
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ド
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5361
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ブック
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5396
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - フォト
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5410
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - キャッシュ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l31-5410
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パイプ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
